warcraftrealms.com 2017-11-30

# Privacy Policy - WarcraftRealms.com

## WarcraftRealms Privacy Policy

### Introduction

WarcraftRealms.com and its affiliates respect the privacy of its on-line visitors and are committed to providing a secure environment for them. We have adopted an On-Line Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store and use the information you provide us. This Privacy Policy details how WarcraftRealms.com safeguards the privacy of its on-line visitors. Please note that when you link to other sites from WarcraftRealms.com, the WarcraftRealms.com Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities on, those other sites. Also, this Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes. 

### Data collection

WarcraftRealms.com only collects online information and will never try to match any offline information. The data collection may take the form of either (1) User registration through the website or forums; (2) Surveys / Polls; (3) Periodic contests. Additionally, your web browser or client software may transmit certain geographic information or information regarding the capabilities or features of your computer to WarcraftRealms.com. WarcraftRealms.com may use this information to generate aggregate statistics about our user community or for security purposes. This information is never linked to you or your household in any way. 

### Information usage

We may use your personal information for internal marketing, profiling, or demographic purposes, so we can adapt our products and services to better suit your needs. We do this to better understand and serve our visitors. Additionally, This information is only to be used by WarcraftRealms.com and not to be sold, or put into the hands of a third party website or company. Please be aware that advertisers or web sites with links to our sites may collect personal information about you. And remember, the WarcraftRealms.com Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, those other advertisers or web sites. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).
